jumpbox.com 2015-06-07

# Our Privacy Policy : VM : Cloud Computing : JumpBox.com | JumpBox Virtual Appliances and Applications for Cloud Computing

JumpBox, Inc. ("JumpBox") values the privacy of our Users, users, members, and others who use [www.jumpbox.com](http://www.jumpbox.com/ "www.jumpbox.com") (the "JumpBox Service") (collectively or individually "Users"). This statement governs information you provide to us or that we learn from your use of the JumpBox Service and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

**The Information JumpBox Collects**

  * _User Provided Information_ : You provide to JumpBox what is generally called "personally identifiable" information when you register and possibly a credit card or other means of payment to or from JumpBox. 
  * _"Cookies" Information_ : When you visit the JumpBox Service, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer. JumpBox uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the JumpBox Service. By using these cookies, we can "remember" what you have done on the JumpBox Service before and personalize our site for you. These persistent types of cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different, so please look through your browser "Help" file to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up. Please note that disabling cookies may prevent you from accessing some of the functionality and site offerings available via the JumpBox Service. 
  * _"Automatically Collected" Information_ : When you visit the JumpBox Service or open one of our HTML emails, we may record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons." This "automatically collected" information may include your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the JumpBox Service, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit. 

**The Way JumpBox Uses Information**  

JumpBox uses the information that we collect to provide to you all of the features and services found on the JumpBox Service. We will use your email address, without further consent, for non-marketing or administrative purposes such as notifying you of major site updates, or for customer service. 

JumpBox uses all of the information that we collect from our Users to understand the usage trends and preferences, to improve the way the JumpBox Service works and looks, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and to create new features and functionality.

JumpBox uses automatically collected information and cookies information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the JumpBox Service; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed.  
JumpBox will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. 

**When JumpBox Discloses Information**

JumpBox may disclose both personally identifiable and automatically collected information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to process such information on our behalf, to provide website maintenance and security, to offer certain features on the JumpBox Service, to assist us in improving the way the JumpBox Service works and looks, and to create new features. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information, and we require these parties to use any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the JumpBox Service. 

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, JumpBox does not share personal information about JumpBox Service users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in JumpBox’s interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

We do not share User information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-out.

**Member Profile and Password**

You have access to your personal information and you may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting User’s member profile access. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. 

**Children**

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen (13) without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides their personal information to JumpBox through the JumpBox Service represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

JumpBox may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the JumpBox Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the JumpBox Service. They automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. 

JumpBox does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. However, please note that if an advertiser asks JumpBox to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. JumpBox’s Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. 

If JumpBox learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the JumpBox Service or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the JumpBox Service. JumpBox may post a notice on the JumpBox Service if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view JumpBox’s Service. JumpBox may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us via email at support -at- jumpbox -dot- com.

**Special Note to International Users**

The JumpBox Service is hosted in the United States. If you are a User accessing the JumpBox Service from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and other regions, and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

**In the Event of Merger or Sale**  

If JumpBox should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information JumpBox receives from you through the JumpBox Service is a JumpBox asset and may be transferred.

**Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "effective date" on the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information that you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the JumpBox Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.  
**  
Contacting JumpBox**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at support -at- jumpbox -dot- com.  
Postal Mail Address: 275 N. Gateway Dr., Ste 131, Phoenix, AZ 85034

If you have a privacy concern regarding the JumpBox Service or this Policy and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the JumpBox Service you should write to support -at- jumpbox -dot- com. You may also leave a comment on the relevant FAQ. In the event that we are still unable to resolve your concerns JumpBox is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution of your privacy concerns.  
Effective Date: 4/19/07
